Lin Juan is a good catch.
لين جوان صفقة جيدة.
Keep an eye on him tomorrow.
راقبه غداً.
Secretary Zhang will go with you.
سيرافقك السكرتير تشانغ.
No.
لا.
The food doesn't taste good anymore.
لم يعد الطعام لذيذاً.
You eat.
أنت تأكل.
I'm going to bed.
سأذهب إلى النوم.
My brother must have done something to my bedtime milk last night.
لا بد أن أخي قد فعل شيئاً بحليبي الذي أتناوله قبل النوم الليلة الماضية.
I slept so deeply.
نمت نوماً عميقاً جداً.
Mr. Wu asked me to go with you
طلب مني السيد وو أن أذهب معك
and see you through the whole event.
وسنكون معكم طوال الحدث.
Well, since you're already here.
حسنًا، بما أنك موجود هنا بالفعل.
Just go along with it.
فقط استسلم للأمر.
I'll just play my part.
سأقوم بدوري فحسب.
So it really is you,
إذن أنت هو فعلاً،
Wu Nongyu.
وو نونجيو.
Senior?
كبير؟
Didn't you form a pact with Mr. Gu?
ألم تعقد اتفاقاً مع السيد غو؟
Last time,
آخر مرة،
I even turned off the lights for you two.
بل إنني أطفأت الأنوار من أجلكما.
So it wouldn't kill the mood.
لذلك لن يفسد ذلك الجو.
What an eyesore.
يا له من منظر بشع!
Well, thanks a lot.
حسنًا، شكرًا جزيلًا.
The fact you're here
حقيقة وجودك هنا
means you never formed a pact with Mr. Gu, right?
هذا يعني أنك لم تعقد اتفاقاً مع السيد غو، أليس كذلك؟
I still have half a year before I turn twenty-five.
لا يزال أمامي نصف عام قبل أن أبلغ الخامسة والعشرين من عمري.
I must get him.
يجب أن أقبض عليه.
You'd better be smart.
من الأفضل أن تكون ذكياً.
Don't compete with me.
لا تنافسني.
While you were asleep,
بينما كنت نائماً،
two rounds were completed.
تم إكمال جولتين.
Those two are the winners.
هذان الاثنان هما الفائزان.
Just pick one Ren
اختر رين واحداً فقط
from among them and get married.
من بينهم ويتزوجون.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
There's another round this morning.
هناك جولة أخرى هذا الصباح.
There will be one more winner.
سيكون هناك فائز آخر.
Stop being so picky.
توقف عن كونك شديد الانتقائية.
You're almost twenty-five too, aren't you?
أنتِ أيضاً على وشك بلوغ الخامسة والعشرين من عمرك، أليس كذلك؟
Time's running out.
الوقت ينفد.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
One would be sentenced to death if they failed to get married by twenty-five?
هل يُحكم على المرء بالإعدام إذا لم يتزوج قبل بلوغه الخامسة والعشرين؟
You really don't know?
ألا تعلم حقاً؟
Once an Yin reaches twenty-five, they must form a pact with a Ren.
بمجرد أن يصل الين إلى خمسة وعشرين، يجب عليه أن يعقد اتفاقاً مع الرين.
Otherwise, organ failure will follow soon.
وإلا، فسيحدث فشل في الأعضاء قريباً.
[Affinity]
[التقارب]
[Border Zone]
[المنطقة الحدودية]
We picked up some leads these past few days.
لقد حصلنا على بعض الخيوط خلال الأيام القليلة الماضية.
The source of the inhibitor smuggling
مصدر تهريب المثبط
may be in Sunset Creek Town.
قد يكون ذلك في بلدة سانست كريك.
Do you need me to go?
هل تريدني أن أذهب؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then I'll send a squad over.
ثم سأرسل فرقة.
I'll head to the Genus to wrap things up.
سأتوجه إلى قسم الأجناس لإنهاء الأمور.
What do you say?
ما رأيك؟
Satisfied with Lin Juan?
هل أنت راضٍ عن لين جوان؟
When an Yin turns twenty-five, the virus erupts.
عندما يبلغ الين الخامسة والعشرين من عمره، ينفجر الفيروس.
Only a Ren's virus can suppress it.
لا يمكن قمعه إلا بواسطة فيروس رين.
You knew all along,
كنت تعلم ذلك طوال الوقت،
didn't you?
أليس كذلك؟
I just wanted you to grow up like an ordinary person,
أردتُ فقط أن تكبر كشخص عادي،
carefree and safe.
بلا هموم وآمن.
I would handle the trouble myself.
سأتولى الأمر بنفسي.
So your solution was
إذن كان الحل الذي قدمته هو
to pick a Ren I barely know,
أن أختار رين الذي بالكاد أعرفه،
then one day tell me outright
ثم أخبرني بذلك صراحةً يوماً ما
that I have to marry him?
هل يجب عليّ أن أتزوجه؟
I've groomed Lin Juan for a long time.
لقد قمت بتدريب لين جوان لفترة طويلة.
He will be loyal to you forever.
سيظل وفياً لك إلى الأبد.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
You don't need to love him.
لستِ مضطرة لأن تحبيه.
Just treat him like a caretaker,
عامله كراعٍ،
or even a blood supply.
أو حتى إمدادات الدم.
Impressive, Wu Siyuan.
مثير للإعجاب، وو سيوان.
Arranged marriage would've died out ages ago
كان الزواج المدبر سيختفي منذ زمن بعيد.
if people like you weren't still propping it up.
لو لم يكن أمثالك لا يزالون يدعمونه.
Keep a close watch on her.
راقبها عن كثب.
Drive
يقود
and take me to the Genus.
وخذني إلى الجنس.
Your virus has been quite active lately.
لقد كان الفيروس لديك نشطًا للغاية مؤخرًا.
Let me stabilize it before you go out.
دعني أصلحها قبل أن تخرج.
♪City lights, hazy lines♪
أضواء المدينة، خطوط ضبابية
♪Lost in you, a singular sin♪
♪ضائع فيك، خطيئة فريدة♪
♪Accomplices in passion♪
♪ شركاء في العاطفة ♪
♪Shared a sweet damnation♪
♪شاركنا لعنة حلوة♪
♪Shed the skin, consequences…♪
♪تخلص من الجلد، والعواقب...♪
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
Whether to ease it or not
سواء كان ذلك لتخفيف الأمر أم لا
is my decision.
هذا قراري.
You have no right to interfere.
ليس لك الحق في التدخل.
♪Watch the game♪
♪شاهد المباراة♪
♪Turn to flames♪
♪تحوّل إلى لهيب♪
♪Just name♪
♪فقط سمِّ♪
♪Who should be blamed♪
♪من يتحمل اللوم؟♪
The final match of the morning is nearing its end.
المباراة الأخيرة لهذا الصباح تقترب من نهايتها.
Here are the current rankings.
إليكم التصنيفات الحالية.
Lin Juan is currently in first place.
لين جوان تحتل المركز الأول حالياً.
[Lin Juan, Today's Rank 1, Defeated Today 12]
[لين جوان، المصنفة الأولى اليوم، هزمت 12 اليوم]
Lin Juan has won five in a row.
حقق لين جوان خمسة انتصارات متتالية.
He's now first across the entire arena.
هو الآن في المركز الأول في جميع أنحاء الساحة.
Is that Lin Juan?
هل هذه لين جوان؟
The final challenger has entered the match.
دخل المتحدي الأخير المباراة.
I'm going to the restroom.
سأذهب إلى دورة المياه.
Challenger, return to the field immediately.
تشالنجر، عد إلى الملعب فوراً.
Take one more step
خطوة أخرى
and we'll open fire.
وسنفتح النار.
I'll go later.
سأذهب لاحقاً.
Let me repeat the rules. (Watch on www.kisskh,la or www.kisskh,id) to Support Admin
دعوني أكرر القواعد. (شاهدوا على www.kisskh.la أو www.kisskh.id) لدعم الإدارة
Only by winning
الفوز هو السبيل الوحيد للفوز
can you enter the mate selection.
هل يمكنك إدخال اختيار الشريك؟
Mr. Gu is mine this time.
السيد غو لي هذه المرة.
Did you hear me?
هل سمعتني؟
Defense barrier rising.
حاجز الدفاع يرتفع.
[Arena]
[الساحة]
Challenge successful.
التحدي ناجح.
Morning winners,
الفائزون في الصباح،
please step in front of the Yin you favor.
يرجى الوقوف أمام الين الذي تفضله.
Please form a pact with me.
أرجو أن تعقد معي اتفاقاً.
I will protect you for the rest of my life.
سأحميك طوال حياتي.
You're not qualified.
أنت غير مؤهل.
Would you reconsider?
هل ستعيد النظر في الأمر؟
So refusal is allowed.
لذا يُسمح بالرفض.
Mm.
مم.
If both sides choose, the marriage process begins.
إذا اختار الطرفان ذلك، تبدأ عملية الزواج.
Otherwise, that Ren returns to the Special Administration Bureau.
وإلا، فإن رين سيعود إلى مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
You have to choose me...
عليك أن تختارني...
Remove the violator's body.
أزل جثة المخالف.
There are always Ren
هناك دائماً رين
who risk everything for freedom.
الذين يخاطرون بكل شيء من أجل الحرية.
What I told you last time,
ما قلته لك في المرة الماضية،
you said you took it in.
قلتَ إنك استوعبت الأمر.
Mm.
مم.
So
لذا
I'm placing my most cherished freedom
أضع حريتي الأثمن بين يدي
in your hands.
بين يديك.
Challenger, return to the field immediately.
تشالنجر، عد إلى الملعب فوراً.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
If I refuse him,
إذا رفضته،
he'll act out again.
سيتصرف بشكل سيء مرة أخرى.
What if he ends up like that Ren?
ماذا لو انتهى به الأمر هكذا يا رين؟
This pact contract is a basic template.
هذا العقد هو نموذج أساسي.
Additional terms can be added as needed.
يمكن إضافة شروط إضافية حسب الحاجة.
The remaining time
الوقت المتبقي
is for you to discuss the pact details.
الأمر متروك لكم لمناقشة تفاصيل الاتفاقية.
Why are you wearing that?
لماذا ترتدين هذا؟
The fight just now left me
المعركة التي خضتها للتو تركتني
overstimulated.
مُفرط التحفيز.
So intense that
شديدة لدرجة
I might lose control.
قد أفقد السيطرة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Right now,
الآن،
I feel calm.
أشعر بالهدوء.
Then
ثم
let's talk terms.
لنتحدث عن الشروط.
First.
أولاً.
I can't form a pact with you.
لا أستطيع عقد اتفاق معك.
We don't truly like each other yet.
نحن لا نحب بعضنا البعض حقاً حتى الآن.
I'll work to make you like me.
سأعمل على أن أجعلك تحبني.
But we can
لكن بإمكاننا
support each other as spouses.
يدعم كل منهما الآخر كزوجين.
You gain freedom
ستحصل على الحرية
and a legal identity.
وهوية قانونية.
I won't be forced by my brother
لن أجبر نفسي على ذلك من قبل أخي
to form a pact with some random Ren.
لعقد اتفاق مع شخص عشوائي يُدعى رين.
Second.
ثانية.
I need your blood for research.
أحتاج إلى دمك لأغراض البحث.
Not much.
ليس كثيراً.
I want to see if I can develop a drug
أريد أن أرى ما إذا كان بإمكاني تطوير دواء
to suppress the virus in my body.
لكبح الفيروس في جسدي.
I'll cooperate.
سأتعاون.
That was quick.
كان ذلك سريعاً.
Any questions,
هل لديك أي أسئلة؟
or reasonable requests?
أو طلبات معقولة؟
I need you to calm me
أحتاج منك أن تهدئني
when I out of control.
عندما أفقد السيطرة.
As for how,
أما عن كيفية ذلك،
the same as at Genus.
كما هو الحال في جينوس.
You can hold me.
يمكنك أن تحتضنني.
But
لكن
kissing needs my permission.
التقبيل يحتاج إلى إذني.
Only if necessary.
فقط عند الضرورة.
♪I cannot breathe♪
♪لا أستطيع التنفس♪
♪Maybe I lost my mind♪
♪ربما فقدت عقلي♪
♪Trying to read your eyes♪
♪أحاول قراءة عينيك♪
♪Console me and hug me♪
♪واسيني واحتضنيني♪
The more I think about it, the worse it feels.
كلما فكرت في الأمر، ازداد شعوري بالسوء.
If you break the contract,
إذا أخلّت بالعقد،
I have no way to stop you.
ليس لدي أي وسيلة لإيقافك.
And can the law really restrain...
وهل يستطيع القانون حقاً أن يقيد...
So you are only realizing now?
إذن أنت تدرك ذلك الآن فقط؟
♪Once chasing shadows, I chose to stop♪
♪بعد أن كنت أطارد الأوهام، اخترت التوقف♪
♪I begged for truths you sealed away♪
♪توسلت إليكِ أن تكشفي لي الحقائق التي أخفيتها عني♪
♪Now I leave into the night♪
♪الآن أغادر إلى الليل♪
♪My heart has shattered…♪
♪ لقد تحطم قلبي…♪
The pact can be kept, only if I want it to.
يمكن الوفاء بالعهد، فقط إذا أردت ذلك.
And right now,
والآن،
I just want you to like me.
أريدك فقط أن تحبني.
♪I am tired of my pride♪
♪لقد سئمت من كبريائي♪
♪Turning cold in the dead of night♪
♪يتحول الجو إلى برد في جوف الليل♪
♪Misreading your kindness♪
♪أسيء فهم لطفك♪
♪Kind soul, let me stay in this heat♪
يا روحًا طيبة، دعني أبقى في هذا الحر
♪Thank you, and goodbye♪
شكراً لكم، وإلى اللقاء!
I don't know how to explain this to Mr. Wu.
لا أعرف كيف أشرح هذا للسيد وو.
Well, I have a question for him too.
حسنًا، لدي سؤال له أيضًا.
Why was there someone not on the list?
لماذا لم يكن هناك شخص ما في القائمة؟
Caught me off guard,
فاجأني الأمر،
and let that kid show off.
ودع ذلك الطفل يتباهى.
So,
لذا،
did it go okay?
هل سارت الأمور على ما يرام؟
Mm.
مم.
Let's start preparing for the wedding.
لنبدأ الاستعدادات لحفل الزفاف.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
You're worried about my brother, right?
أنت قلق على أخي، أليس كذلك؟
All he cares about is me forming a pact with a Ren.
كل ما يهمه هو أن أعقد اتفاقاً مع رين.
As long as I do it, he'll accept it.
طالما أنني أفعل ذلك، فسوف يتقبله.
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
Don't let my brother know
لا تدع أخي يعرف
I've chosen someone else just yet.
لقد اخترت شخصًا آخر حتى الآن.
I'll explain it to him later.
سأشرح له ذلك لاحقاً.
But...
لكن...
I agree as well.
وأنا أوافق أيضاً.
Your sibling issues are yours to handle.
مشاكلك مع إخوتك هي مسؤوليتك وحدك.
Don't drag me into it.
لا تورطني في هذا الأمر.
Besides,
بجانب،
it's not like no one wants me.
ليس الأمر كما لو أن لا أحد يريدني.
Thanks for understanding.
شكراً لتفهمكم.
Mr. Wu won't be back until the wedding day.
لن يعود السيد وو إلا يوم الزفاف.
We'll handle the preparations together.
سنتولى الاستعدادات معًا.
And of course, all you need to do is cooperate.
وبالطبع، كل ما عليك فعله هو التعاون.
I'll give it my all.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
As if I would.
وكأنني سأفعل.
Will this really make my face look smaller?
هل سيجعل هذا وجهي يبدو أصغر حقاً؟
Miss, don't worry.
يا آنسة، لا تقلقي.
It's a key step to becoming a beautiful bride.
إنها خطوة أساسية لتصبح عروساً جميلة.
Is this garment even made for humans?
هل هذا الثوب مصمم أصلاً للبشر؟
The size is too small.
المقاس صغير جدًا.
There's no time to let it out.
ليس هناك وقت لتفريغها.
You'll have to eat less for a while.
سيتعين عليك تناول كميات أقل من الطعام لفترة من الوقت.
Please.
لو سمحت.
[Pork Trotter Rice Bowl]
[طبق أرز مع أرجل الخنزير]
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪